—— HILDAH MARINGA —— DATA ANALYST

CONTACT

Phone Number:

+254 716730550

Email:

maringahildah85@gmail.com

PROFILE

A meticulous and focused data analyst with exceptional analytical and problem-solving skills and a strongability to interpret data and draw meaningful conclusions. Experienced in data analysis techniques, such as statistical modeling, machine learning, and predictive analysis

SKILLS

- EXCEL
- SOL AND DATABASES
- PYTHON
- R PROGRAMMING
- GOOGLE ANALYTICS
- MACHINE LEARNING
- TABLEAU
- POWER BI

EDUCATION

TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY OF MOMBASA

September, 2020 - August, 2024

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics and Computer Science.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Data Analytics

Google Advanced Data Analysis

REFERENCES

Richard Gachoki

Network Engineer Safaricom PLC

Phone: +254 7 01 390 175 Email: richgachoki@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYST INTERN – Office of the Data Protection Commissioner.

October 2023 - Present

- Conducted data audits to ensure compliance with data protection standards, enhancing data security protocols across departments.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to analyze and interpret data, driving insights that improved policy decision-making.

DATA ANALYST INTERN- Our Lady of Lourdes Mwea Hospital

September 2023 – December 2023

- Cleaned and transformed raw datasets of patients' records into structured formats for further analysis.
- Conducted end-to-end analysis to identify gaps in the hospital's management and propose solutions.
- Interpreted data and analyzed results using tools like Excel and SQL.

ANALYSTS' CLUB, MOMBASA

April 2022 – November 2023

- Worked with team members to identify problems around us, collected data, and made analyses to come up with the best solutions.
- Generated forecasts and projections based on historical data.